[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Normal blood pressure levels are higher for older patients.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What maintains the male secondary sex characteristics?", "correct_answer": "androgen", "incorrect_answers": ["epididymis", "vas deferens", "testes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the first grasses evolve?", "correct_answer": "55 million years ago", "incorrect_answers": ["35 million years ago", "65 million years ago", "200 million years ago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word means a detailed record of a persons life.", "correct_answer": "Dossier", "incorrect_answers": ["Denouement", "Dreeour", "Deluge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Besides containing vitamin E, this fruit also has many carotenoids, especially Beta-carotene, which helps you cope with harmful sun rays.", "correct_answer": "Mango", "incorrect_answers": ["Banana", "Apple", "Cucumber"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is considered the major enemy of the wolf in the wild, apart from humans?", "correct_answer": "Other wolves", "incorrect_answers": ["Bear", "Eagle", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the hit movie Anchorman, Veronica is introduced to the news team at a meeting in which diversity is discussed.  What does Ron Burgundy think diversity is?", "correct_answer": "An old, old wooden ship", "incorrect_answers": ["An arsonist with oddly shaped feet", "A whales genitalia", "A wedding on top of a mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the ligament that attaches to the head of the femur and the acetabulum.", "correct_answer": "Ligamentum Teres", "incorrect_answers": ["Ligamentus Trigemini", "Ligamentum Tores", "Ligamentus Iliopsoas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do male lions have which females do not possess?", "correct_answer": "A mane", "incorrect_answers": ["An extra tooth", "Longer nails", "Distinguished eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to self-discipline and refraining from worldly pleasures?", "correct_answer": "Asceticism", "incorrect_answers": ["Aneurysm", "Ableism", "Atavism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest organ in the human body?", "correct_answer": "Skin", "incorrect_answers": ["Stomach", "None of these", "Large intestine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what climate zone does the popular Parasol mushroom grow?", "correct_answer": "Temperate", "incorrect_answers": ["Tropical", "All of these", "Boreal"]}]